

## Nikola Jurková

## **Junior Front-End Developer**

linkedin.com/in/nikola-jurkova nikolajur.github.io/portfolio nikola.jurkova@email.cz

+420 774 567 959

I'm a self-taught front-end developer with a background in Geographic Information Systems. I believe in lifelong learning - I'm passionate about developing new skills. I've been learning to code and working on my projects since 2022. It's time to accept a new challenge and start a career in IT!

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2022/1 - 2023/2

2021/1 - 2021/12

2019/4 - 2021/11

2018/2 - 2019/1

2008/8 - 2018/1

# Career Break Tenerife, Spain

- self-education in programming (online courses, own projects) & traveling

#### <u>Geographic Information System Specialist</u> Land Survey Office, Prague, Czechia

- geospatial data analysis
- creating workflows for regular data updates (inc. Python scripting)

#### **Geodata Specialist**

**Self-Employed** 

- geospatial data processing & old maps analysis

#### **Career Break**

**British Columbia & Nova Scotia, Canada** 

- work in restaurants & traveling

### **Geographic Information System Specialist**

Prague Institute of Planning and Development, Czechia

- administration of Prague's geodata
- web mapping services
- data vizualization/cartography

#### **EDUCATION**



<u>Master of Science, Physical Geography and Geoecology</u> University of Ostrava, Faculty of Science

<u>Erasmus Programm - student exchange</u> University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

#### **HOBBIES**

- traveling and travel itinerary planning, maps, hiking, swimming, coding, languages, asian cuisine, history

#### SKILLS























#### **LANGUAGES**



German